<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Recycle and Me</string>
    <string name="start_app">Lets Begin</string>
    <string name="plastic_identifiers">Plastic Number Identifiers</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">SettingsActivity</string>
    <string name="channel_name">Encourage User</string>
    <string name="channel_description">Display encouragement</string>

    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="pref_title_theme">Dark theme</string>
    <string name="pref_description_theme">Turn on dark theme</string>
    <string name="pref_none">None</string>
    <string name="title_activity_pininfo_page">PINInfoPage</string>
    <string name="PET">
        "Polyethylene terephthalate (PET/PETE) is one of the most commonly used plastics in "
        "consumer products.\n"
        "It has a low risk of leaching (when chemicals from the plastics transfer into the food) "
        "and is FDA approved. \n"
        "The benefits of PTE include: lightweight, smooth, shatter resistant, and can withstand "
        "temperatures ranging from -20 F to 120 F. \n\n"

        "PET products: Soft drinks, water bottles, clear hinged containers, peanut butter "
        "containers, salad dressing bottles, and oven-ready cooking trays \n\n"

        "Proper disposal: Rinsed and dried \n\n"

        "Method of disposal: Curbside recycle programs"
    </string>

    <string name="HDPE">
    "High-density polyethylene (HDPE) is another commonly used plastic that differentiates itself "
        "by being more durable/flexible than other plastic types. \n"
    "It has a low risk of leaching and is safe to be reused. \n"
    "The benefits of HDPE include: Stiff, durable, affordable, and can withstand "
    "temperatures ranging from -40 F to 266 F. \n\n"

    "HDPE products: Milk jugs, juice bottles, cleaner bottles, trash can liners, and flower pots\n\n"

    "Proper disposal: Rinsed and dried\n\n"

    "Method of disposal: Curbside recycle programs"
    </string>

    <string name="PVC">
    "Polyvinyl chloride (PVC) comes in two basic forms, rigid and flexible. Like HDPE, PVC is very "
        "durable. It's rigid form is often used in construction and its flexible form can be found"
    "in many household products and appliances. \n\n"

    "The benefits of PVC include: durable, weather resistant, non-conductive, chemical resistant, "
    "and can withstand temperatures ranging from -0 F to 150 F. \n\n"

    "Some PVC products: Window cleaner bottles, detergent bottles, garden hoses, pipe, "

    "Proper disposal: N/A \n\n"

    "Method of disposal: Look up a local recycling center or non-profit who will take it"
    </string>

    <string name="LDPE">
    "Low-density polyethylene (LDPE) is a safe product to reuse and won't leach any chemicals."
    " Unlike its counterpart HDPE, LDPE is quite flexible when compared to most plastics. \n"
    " \n"
    "The benefits of LDPE include: , smooth, shatter resistant, and can withstand "
    "temperatures ranging from -58 F to 185 F. \n\n"

    "LDPE products: Plastic bread bags. food wrappings, squeezable bottles, and cereal bags\n\n"

    "Proper disposal: No contaminants/Washed and rinsed\n\n"

    "Method of disposal: Curbside recycle programs"
    </string>

    <string name="PP">
    "Polypropylene (PP) is known to handle high-temperatures better than most plastics so often"
    "you'll find it used for hot liquids and foods. A good identifier for PP would be how clear the"
        " product is. Often polypropylene is clear. \n\n"

    "The benefits of PP include: durable, lightweight, high melting point, and can withstand "
    "temperatures ranging from 0 F to 250 F. \n\n"

    "PP products: Take out containers, plates/bowls, straws, auto parts, and cups\n\n"

    "Proper disposal: Rinsed and Dried\n\n"

    "Method of disposal: Becoming increasingly accepted by curbside recycling programs so check, "
        "but a good program that accepts these plastics by mail is Preserve Gimme 5."
    </string>

    <string name="PS">
   "Polystyrene (PS) is a bit of an odd plastic. It is considered recyclable but cost wise it "
    "isn't. Another word for this product you may know is styrofoam, which is a stretched/expanded "
        "version of polystyrene. \n\n"

    "The benefits of PS include: lightweight, versatile, cheap, and can withstand "
    "temperatures ranging from 20 F to 180 F. \n\n"

    "PS products: Disposable plates, disposable cups, egg cartons, straws, and shipping pellets\n\n"

    "Proper disposal: N/A (Read below)\n\n"

    "Method of disposal: N/A as polystyrene isn't accepted as it is lightweight but doesn't break "
        "down easily. Recycling is calculated by weight so it isn't profitable to accept."
    </string>

    <string-array name="PINlist">
        <item>@string/PET</item>
        <item>@string/HDPE</item>
        <item>@string/PVC</item>
        <item>@string/LDPE</item>
        <item>@string/PP</item>
        <item>@string/PS</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

</resources>